So let's combine our reducers, we got two, burger builder and order. So in the index.js file in our application,
Bu yzden, Berger bowlingerine atfettiimiz indirgeyicileri birletirip, indeks paylamlarnn uygulamanza dmesi iin sipari verelim.
now it's time to combine reducers.
imdi indirgeyicileri birletirme zaman.
So first of all, let's import combineReducers from the redux package, then I want to import my second
Her eyden nce reader X paketinden redktrleri ithal edelim, o zaman ikinci
reducer so I'll import my orderReducer from ./storeReducersOrder and now I can combine both.
reticisini ithal etmek istiyorum, bylece sipari redktrn nokta eik izgi maazas redktr sipariinden ie aktarabilir ve imdi her ikisini de birletirebilirim.
So what I'll do is I'll creates a new constant here, routeReducer because they are combined into one
Dolaysyla ne yapacam hepsi yeni bir sabit rota drcs yaratyor nk burada kullanclarla birletirilen renilmi
reducer as you learned, call combineReducers here and pass a javascript object.
bir ar olarak bir kullancya birletiriliyor ve bir javascript nesnesi iletiyorlar.
And there, I can now just pass burger builder and assign that burger builder reducer and order and assign
Ve imdi sadece Bergere Boulder' geebilir ve Bergen Bolla azaltcy atayabilir ve emri emir ve
the order reducer,
tayin edebilirim.
the two things we import and the root reducer is then what I passed to create store. With that, the whole
Kaba redktrlerde aldmz iki ey maazamz yaratmak iin getiimizden daha ok ey
application will break because now we have different slices of state, burger builder and order.
kryor nk imdi devlet burger Boulder ve sipariinin farkl dilim var.
So I need to go to my containers and update, in the burger builder container, the bottom where I reach out
Bu yzden konteynerlerime gitmem lazm ve burger Bolar konteynrn, devlet mallarnn toplam fiyatna
to state ingredients total price and error,
ve hatasna ulatm alt ksmn gncellemeliyim.
this should all be state burger builder ingredients and the same for total price and error. In the checkout
Bu, devlet burger reticisi bileenleri olmal ve ayn zamanda, devlet burgeri Bolar ierik maddeleri ve ierik
container where I also get the ingredients, that should be state burger builder ingredients, in the
maddelerine ulatm iletiim veri konteyneri gereken malzemeleri alacaklar deme konteyneri
contact data container where I reach out to the ingredients
toplam fiyat ve hata iin ayn olmaldr.
too, this should also be state burger builder ingredients in state burger builder
Devlet burger Buller'da devlet burger cesur katklar olmalsn.
total price but the loading here is coming from the orders, so this should be state orders loading to
Toplam fiyat ancak ykleme burada siparilerden geliyor, bu durumun yklenmesi veya sadece bu mlkn kullanmn sipari
use, oh just order excuse me, to just order to use that property
etmek iin beni balamann emri sipari edilmesi gerektiini belirtti.
so just state order or loading. With that we can save all these files and go back to the application, looks
Yani sadece devlet sipari bir yk tm bu dosyalar kaydedebilir ve uygulamaya geri dnmek iyi
good,
grnyor.
this still works. If we now continue,
Devam edersek bu yine de geerli.
let's see if we can successfully dispatch an action here.
Bakalm burada bir ilemi baaryla gnderebilir miyiz.
So here I'll enter some test demo data,
Yani burada baz test demo verileri giriyorsunuz.
just something we can submit, test@test.com, let's click order.
Gelecekteki testte test gnderebileceimiz bir ey var ve tklama emrini verelim.
We saw the loading screen,
Ykleme ekrann grdk.
we get something back from the server, that's looking good,
yi grnml sunucudan bir eyler alyoruz.
let's have a look at redux,
Oku x'e de byle bakyorum.
I see at least one thing which won't work as expected,
Beklendii gibi almayacak en azndan bir ey gryorum.
we get purchaseBurgerStart and we saw the spinner for a second, so that worked and purchaseBurgerSuccess
Chase Bergere ncesi balang yaptk ve bir saniyeliine spinner' grdk ve bylece
and in success, we see all that the orders were updated, that we added this new object here where
Chase'in ilerleme kaydettiini ve baarya ulatn grdk ve tm siparilerin gncellendiini grdk ve bu yeni nesneyi burada bizim
we have our ingredients and then stored some data in it.
malzemelerimiz var ve ardndan depoladmz baz yerlerde sakladk iindeki veri.
If we have a look at the state,
Eyalete bir gz atn.
we can expand our orders,
Emirlerimizi geniletebiliriz.
have a look at that order and we see that this order here,
Siparie bir gz atn ve bu sipariin burada olduunu gryoruz.
I think I need to make this a bit broader to see all of it has an ID which is not correct,
Sanrm bunu doru olmayan bir kimliine sahip olup olmadn grmek iin biraz daha geni yapmam gerekiyor.
I should have extracted the name property so that's one thing we need to adjust.
Ayarlamam gereken bir ey olmas iin isim mlkiyetini de karmalydm.
Besides that, all of that seems to be working
Bunun yan sra hepsi ie yaryor gibi grnyor.
rather good,
Robert iyi.
of course we're not redirected once we're done.
imiz bittiinde elbette ynlendirilmeziz.
So this id fix and being redirected, that are the things I want to fix,
Dolaysyla bu fikir dnyor ve dzeltmek istediim iki ey olduunu dnyor ve ynlendiriyor.
let's just check quickly if it did work on the backend too
Arka uta da ie yarayp yaramayacan hemen kontrol edelim.
but obviously it did, we wouldn't have gotten an id otherwise.
Ancak belli ki baka trl bir fikre kaplmamalydk.
So that's looking all good,
Bu yzden hepsi iyi grnyor.
we got a burger here.
Burada bir burger var.
Delivery method wasn't passed on I see,
Teslimat metodu gemedi grnd.
so that is something we should also fix
Bu da dzeltmeniz gereken bir ey.
but besides that, looking good. So let's fix all these things and let's then see what else we can do in our
Ancak iyi grnml yan sra, bunlar tamir edelim ve uygulamamzda baka neler
application.
yapabileceimizi grelim.
Let's quickly fix the issues we found,
Bulduumuz sorunlar hzla dzeltelim.
one is in the contact data here where we submit the form,
Biri, formu gnderdiimiz balam verileri ierisindedir.
the thing is, if we never adjust the dropdown value then the value is empty
Asl ey alan deerini ayarlamazsak deer bo olur.
and it shouldn't be,
Ve yle olmamal.
it should be let's say fastest, by default.
Varsaylan olarak en hzl diyelim.
So I just added this to the value property in the delivery method
Bu yzden teslim yntemindeki Value zelliine ekledim.
object in the state of the contact data,
rtibat verisi durumundaki nesne.
that's one important adjustment to have this work correctly. Now
Bu, nemli bir ayarlamann imdi dzgn almasn salyor.
one other thing is in the reducer in order.js, when we have a success and we get the id, here action order
Her ey azaltcda srasyla J. bulunur. S. ne zaman bir baar elde edersek ve
ID, that's the wrong ID because in the order file in the actions folder where we pass on the ID, I pass
burada bir eylem kimlii ID kimlii yanl kimlii olur nk sipari dosyasnda ve kimlii getiimiz eylemler klasrnde
on response data as the ID
yant durumu kimlii olarak geiyorum.
but instead, we just saw in the log that its on the name property on the data, that is the ID we want
Ancak onun yerine, sadece kilitte, saklamak istediimiz kimliiyle ilgili verilerin Name zellii zerinde
to store.
olduunu grdk.
But with that, we have this working the only missing thing is that we redirect it, re-route and that is
Ancak bununla birlikte alyoruz, eksik olan tek ey, yolumuza yn verdik ve bir sonraki
something I'll do in the next lecture.
dersimizde yapacamz bir ey.